<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Submission1</string>

    <string-array name="club_name">
        <item>Barcelona FC</item>
        <item>Real Madrid FC</item>
        <item>Bayern Munchen FC</item>
        <item>Manchester City FC</item>
        <item>Manchester United FC</item>
        <item>Chelsea FC</item>
        <item>AC Milan FC</item>
        <item>Arsenal FC</item>
    </string-array>

    <array name="club_image">
        <item>@drawable/img_barca</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_madrid</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_bayern</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_city</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_mu</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_chelsea</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_acm</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_arsenal</item>
    </array>

    <string-array name="club_desc">
        <item>Barcelona is one of three founding members of the Primera División that have never been relegated from the top division since its inception in 1929, along with Athletic Bilbao and Real Madrid. In 2009, Barcelona became the first Spanish club to win the continental treble consisting of La Liga, Copa del Rey, and the UEFA Champions League, and also became the first Spanish football club to win six out of six competitions in a single year, by also winning the Spanish Super Cup, UEFA Super Cup and FIFA Club World Cup</item>
        <item>Real Madrid Club de Fútbol, umumnya dikenal sebagai Real Madrid, adalah klub sepak bola profesional yang berbasis di Madrid, Spanyol. Didirikan pada tahun 1902 sebagai Madrid Football Club, secara tradisional mengenakan kostum kandang putih.</item>
        <item>FC Bayern was founded in 1900 by 11 football players, led by Franz John.[5] Although Bayern won its first national championship in 1932,[6] the club was not selected for the Bundesliga at its inception in 1963.[7] The club had its period of greatest success in the middle of the 1970s when, under the captaincy of Franz Beckenbauer, it won the European Cup three times in a row (1974–1976). Overall, Bayern has reached ten European Cup/UEFA Champions League finals, most recently winning their fifth title in 2013 as part of a continental treble.</item>
        <item>Manchester City Football Club is a football club in Manchester, England. Founded in 1880 as St. Mark's, it became Ardwick Association Football Club in 1887 and Manchester City in 1894</item>
        <item>Manchester United Football Club, commonly known as Man United or simply United, is a professional football club based in Old Trafford, Greater Manchester, England, that competes in the Premier League, the top flight of English football.</item>
        <item>Chelsea Football Club is a professional football club in London, England, that competes in the Premier League. Founded in 1905, the club's home ground since then has been Stamford Bridge.</item>
        <item>Associazione Calcio Milan, sering disebut sebagai A.C. Milan atau hanya Milan, adalah sebuah klub sepak bola Italia yang berbasis di Milan, Lombardia, yang bermain di Serie A.</item>
        <item>Arsenal Football Club is a professional football club based in Islington, London, England, that plays in the Premier League, the top flight of English football.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
